WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
A hot spring?
Yeah, just off of this road
there's a nice town with a hot spring.
Yunosato Hot Springs...
They say it does a world of good
for fatigue and beauty.
Aren't we going straight home?
Everyone's waiting!
Naruto's right.
Our hometown is in
a state of emergency,
there's no time to procrastinate.
It won't make much difference
if we're one or two days late...
It's really popular with girls,
and it's mixed bathing...
Hey?! Pervy Sage?
Sometimes it's necessary for humans
to take breathers.
We'll take one bath!
That's not what you said before!
It's okay. Well, let's go!
That's her, no mistake.
We've finally... found her.
Naruto's
Strange
Hot Springs Side Trip
We have the pleasure of
a visit from four people and one piglet.
— Welcome!
Even though this has mixed bathing...
"good children should not copy him"
I'm all alone with this brat.
I'm so unlucky.
Well then, shall we play pachinko
or something?
We have plenty of time before dinner.
You're not going to the hot spring?
If we go right now, there are fools...
So, let's go, let's go.
I'm going to get out already.
Not yet, not yet.
Not until the girls get here.
Oh, I see...
Well, c'mon girls.
All of you, come on...
Welcome!
Ah, that was refreshing.
W-We've been robbed!
The necklace I got from
Grandma Tsunade is gone!
Where! Where is it?!
"If you want your necklace back,
give back the money"?
"We'll wait at the three cedars on
the mountain behind."
Signed, the Akagi Family.
Money?
What are they talking about?
Girls came in, all right.
But...
they're all female monkeys!
I want to bathe with people.
Hey, here I am!
Come out! Akagi Family!
What do you want, kid?!
That's my line!
I haven't borrowed any money
from you people!
So give me my necklace back!
"My" necklace?
Did we mistake his stuff
for that woman's?
Ah, that's it!
Give it back!
W-Wait!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Go!
You thieves!
— Take this!
— Go!
H-Help...
People came, all right...
But...
They're all men!
— Bring it on!
— Cheers!
I want to bathe with women...
Huh? So the one who borrowed money
is Grandma Tsunade?
Yes... nicknamed
the "Legendary Sitting Duck".
She played at the Akagi gambling den
until she was penniless.
We loaned her what she lost.
That's right, and there's an I.O.U.
Wha...?! There are so many zeros!
I'm Senta, this guy is called Bunzo.
The boss ordered us to collect
on the debt three years ago...
We set out on a journey
from Akagi Mountain
prepared not to return
until we get the money back.
We've heard rumors about
the lady here and there...
But, she sure was something.
She was elusive and quite hard to find.
Then recently, we caught
some information that she'd appeared.
We were waiting on
the side of the road...
That's when we came along
with Grandma Tsunade.
But why did you raid the room
so stealthily?
Rumor has it
that ordinary means don't work
against the "Legendary Sitting Duck."
We didn't think that
if we tried to collect amicably,
she would pay us.
She's certainly stingy...
We heard that she cherished the necklace
next to her life,
so we thought she'd pay
in exchange for it.
No way. After all, you raided my room.
We never even dreamed that the owner
of the necklace would have changed...
Err... Can't you ask the lady to pay?
Uh, even you say so...
Please! If we don't get the money back,
we can't go home!
Our wives and kids are waiting for us
to come home!
— Please... I'm begging you!
It's all gone...
Bad luck...
damn it. I'm stone broke.
Well, let's call it quits with pachinko.
It's about time for a bath...
— Shizune...
— Yes?
My bag is at the front desk of the inn.
What?!
Y-You can't mean to bring it here?!
Everything to your name is in it...
I've just lost! I can't repress this
feeling!
Just bring it without complaint.
Yes, ma'am!
Huh? Could you be...
Y-You are...!
There are women, all right...
But...
I was hoping for younger,
more titillating women...
This one, right?
Thank you...
Are you with Ms Tsunade?
Yes.
This came for her not long ago...
To Tsunade
A letter? I wonder who could've...?
Tsunade-sama! Tsunade-sama!
Tsunade-sama!
Huh? Tsunade-sama!
She's not here...
Okay, Tonton...
You know to search for
Tsunade-sama, right!
What, impossible? Why?
I see! The smell of the sulfur
from the hot spring interferes...
Well then, the only way
to search for her is on foot!
Tsunade-sama!
Tsunade-sama! Tsunade-sama!
Where are you!
We have a problem!
Tsunade-sama!
Oh, what in the world should I do?
We have Uzumaki Naruto.
If you want him returned unharmed,
please return all of the money you owe!
We'll wait by the three cedars on
the mountain behind. The Akagi Family
What should I do?
I have to help Naruto.
On top of that, if it's discovered
that Tsunade-sama has a huge debt,
talk of her installment as
the Fifth Hokage will probably end.
That's right, we have
to handle this by ourselves.
Right, Tonton?
Do you think it's going to work out well?
No problem.
Here she comes.
Grandma Tsunade!
Stop!
You know who we are, right?
You're the henchmen of the Akagi.
Then I'll make it brief.
Pay back your debt
in one lump sum.
Or else...
his life is over!
Help me!
Whatever.
His life doesn't matter much to me.
— Huh!
— What did you just say?!
Well then, the money...
Why did it come to this?
This isn't titillating,
this is just tight!
Drats! Let me have patience!
Didn't you hear me?
It doesn't matter to me
what happens with his life.
You... damn old hag!
Was what I would have said,
until just a little bit ago, I think.
Once I become the Hokage,
he'd be a precious subordinate.
I can't leave him in this mess.
Grandma Tsunade...
Right now, this is all I've got.
Take it.
Let me make sure of this.
I don't mean it's paid off in full,
but that'll do it for the interest, right?
Fake!
You're not going to pay
the money back?
It's none of your business.
These guys can't go home!
Don't you feel sorry for them!
You couldn't possibly?
In that case, I'll have to use force
to get it back!
Naruto's Shadow Clones?!
I see, Naruto has joined hands
with the Akagi Family...
So, where did Naruto and company go?
As expected...
I didn't think she'd hand
the money over meekly.
But to be that much of a coward...
What should we do?
Grandma Tsunade has a huge suitcase.
No doubt there's money in it.
We have to do something
to get our hands on that suitcase.
Shoot!
I'm supposed to be kidnapped,
and she's casually drinking alcohol.
It's that suitcase.
How do we get it out?
Leave it to me.
Tsunade-sama, you've returned.
Ah, here's the suitcase.
It's dangerous,
so let's leave it at the front desk.
Well then...
Look, I went and got it!
— You did it!
Grandma Tsunade!
Shoot... If you're the Hokage...
If you're the Hokage,
then pay your debt back
like a Hokage would!
A Hokage is meant
to protect everyone!
These guys can't return to their home,
they are desperate!
Why don't you do something?!
Naruto...
Or do people from other countries
not matter to you?
That kind of Hokage...
I cannot accept!
Now!
Here!
Hurry up and run away!
— Right!
— Okay!
Oh, she's already catching up!
It's all or nothing!
Huh?
— You did it!
Tonton?!
Naruto!
Just hand over the suitcase! Or else!
F-Fork over the suitcase!
If we take a direct hit from
Grandma Tsunade's attack,
then it's over!
Out of the way, out of the way!
Purse snatchers?
Excuse us!
Hey what's going on?!
Hey! Don't cause trouble
for the general public!
It's because you're following us!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What's going on...?
Naruto, we leave it up to you.
This is no good.
If the contents of that suitcase
become known,
That's right, that happened too.
And I was young then too.
Gulp it down.
Excuse me, Boss.
What is it? You're in front of a guest.
W-Well...
A clone!
That's a clone too?
Wrong again.
Sheesh, which is the real one?!
The rest...
— Where are the rest?!
Over there!
— Hold it!
— Naruto!
— Wait!
Prepare yourself!
Shoot, let me go! Let me go!
Settle down!
G-Got it!
The money!
Okay, they got it!
IOU's?!
It's not money?!
— Oh no...
— This is too much!
What are you doing?!
This is in the middle of town!
Huh!
T-Two Old Ladies?!
You're mixed up in
this commotion as well?
I'd like to hear your reason
for it, Shizune!
Hello... Tsunade-sama...
What?! Shizune...
And you guys belong to the Akagi.
B-Boss Jirocho!
Who?
You don't know?!
He's the number one gang boss,
Jirocho from the Land of Tea!
He's an old friend of mine.
As luck would have it,
we met by accident on the street.
You're Bunzo and Senta
if I'm not mistaken.
Just in time.
I have something to say to you!
— What?!
You mean the debt to the Akagi Family?
I paid it back a year ago.
Is that true?
That was last year,
when we were near Akagi's.
Did you forget?
I-I'm sorry.
Hey!
It's a circular from Akagi
addressed to me.
I'll just read the part addressed to you.
"Senta and Bunzo,
"The debt is paid, come home soon."
Signed, Shugoro Akagi.
See?
You've gotta be kidding.
All that energy spent, for nothing.
— Thank you for helping us.
— Now we can go home relieved.
Go in good spirits.
— You too, Naruto. Take care!
Hey, if the suitcase
doesn't have money in it,
why were you so serious
about getting it back?
That's...
If the IOU's were discovered
by the people in the village,
they'll oppose Tsunade-sama's
installment as Hokage.
You worry too much.
The Hokage and the debt
are unrelated.
Not only that,
she said she returned the money,
so there's nothing to worry about.
At least the Akagi debt was...
What?
Don't worry, don't worry!
What? We forgot something?
Finally, the time has come.
Communal bathing with girls...
Patience paid off...
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
You're awesome,
Grandma Tsunade!
Kakashi-sensei and Sasuke
are all right now!
You can't rejoice yet.
The current situation
in the village is serious.
You're right.
I have to do my best,
And work hard for
the village as well.
Hey! N-Naruto,
where do you think you're going?!
I have to fill my stomach first!
You have no sense of emergency...
Next time:
"Tsunade's Announcement! Quit Being a Ninja."
What is that supposed to mean?!